(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Hello, sir.
Hello.
What is your name, sir?
Where are you from?
My name is Dr. N.
Rajagopal.
Okay.
I am a retired Government College Principal and
Joint Director.
Super, sir.
Okay.
Good profile, sir.
So, how excited are you to attend this
event, sir?
I have attended this first event.
Okay.
This is the second event.
I joined this health school more than a
year and a half ago.
Super, sir.
Super.
To attend this event, I and my son's
family were in America.
Okay.
Since I told you that there is an
award in this event, Okay.
I had to return to America in November.
Okay.
For this event, for this award, Okay.
I cancelled it, advanced the ticket and came
here and got this award yesterday.
Super, sir.
You have really put in a lot of
effort.
Super, sir.
Thank you very much for coming.
So, what do you feel about getting this
award, sir?
To get this award, in the last event,
I took it as a goal and told
the doctor.
You took it as a goal.
Next year, I will get this award in
the same place in your hands.
Super.
Before that, since I am a retired principal,
Okay.
Since I was in the teaching course, Okay.
A teacher should listen to what the student
says.
Okay.
I followed it sincerely.
I followed Level 1 completely and correctly.
At that time, my weight reduced to 5
kgs.
5 kgs reduced.
Okay.
All my diabetes was controlled.
After completing Level 2, my weight reduced to
12 kgs.
Other than that, HbA1c, before Level 1, Okay.
It was 9.7 kgs.
Okay.
After completing Level 2, it reduced to 5
.5 kgs.
After joining My Health School?
Everything happened only because of My Health School,
Dr. Prabhakar sir and Dr. Oh, sorry, Sudhakar
sir, Engineering Sudhakar sir.
Sudhakar and Prabhakar.
They are truly magicians, sir.
Definitely, sir.
There is no doubt about it.
How was the mindset session, sir?
The mindset session was wonderful.
Sometimes, it used to happen in the night.
Okay.
During the mindset session, when he used to
speak, I used to listen to him sincerely.
Sometimes, I used to feel sleepy.
He used to say, I used to feel
sleepy for some people.
Then, it happened.
In the morning, they used to do it
again.
Okay.
I used to do it again.
You used to do it again.
To that extent, it was an inducement.
It created an impact.
Okay.
It created.
It created for everything.
Super.
If you join My Health School, it will
be great for sure.
Definitely, sir.
Definitely, they can come out of the disease.
They can.
Okay.
Fine, sir.
Sir, what is the name of your health
coach?
Please tell us about them.
I don't remember the name of the person
who was in Level 1.
Okay.
In Level 2, there was Mrs. Rithi.
How did she support you?
She used to ask me, sir, whether I
am getting better or not.
Even then, in Level 2, Okay.
I told her, I am allergic to millets,
madam.
Okay, sir.
She asked me to ask her.
Once in two days, she will ask me,
sir, I asked her, which millet allergy do
you have, leave that, and take the rest
of the millets, Okay.
She asked me to take that.
She used to ask me, sir, now that
you have left all that, there are other
millets, is it okay now?
How do you feel?
Just repeatedly, repeatedly, she was in touch with
me.
She cooperated with you and supported you.
She cooperated with me.
After that, I joined Hackathon.
Hackathon, okay.
In Hackathon, there was Mrs. Swetha.
Okay.
She was more than this.
She was from our group, Pioneers group.
Okay.
She called me and asked, sir, did you
post today?
Did you finish that challenge today?
Did you finish all the questions?
She would ask you every day.
She would ask me every day.
Good response.
These are all highly encouraging for the mild
students.
Super, sir.
Thank you very much, sir.
It was very nice.
Okay.
For my health school, for Dr. Farmer, for
his brother Sudhakar, for my family, for my
son's family, for all of them, for friends,
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Sir, this is an important question.
Sir, many people like you are diabetic patients.
For 10-15 years, they have been taking
tablets for diabetes.
They have been seeing doctors.
Even if they know about my health school,
they have some doubts.
Sir, is it useful for us?
Should we join this?
They have doubts.
So, to such people, sir?
I have told some of them, what I
am saying is, it is possible.
If you go with that belief, in my
health school, not only diabetic patients, all other
diseases, medicines, when it comes to food, medicines,
they will make everything right for us.
I am an example for that.
I have already said that.
Hereafter, what I am saying is, that is
it.
Come with faith.
Definitely, you will get rid of the diseases.
You will be very healthy.
You will live happily.
Ok.
Thank you very much, sir.
Last question, sir.
So, anything to Dr. Prabhakar sir, please look
at the camera and say it.
After the show, I will definitely start.
I will inform him.
Dr. Prabhakar sir, your effort is very, very
wonderful.
For this society, for the human society, you
will keep on saying often, within this year
2030, for the society one crore people, within
this year 2030, should get rid of the
diseases and serve them.
Your service should grow more and more.
You serve everyone with your heart.
To get rid of the diseases by serving
with your heart, you should work as a
companion like God.
I pray with my heart, sir.
Prabhakar sir, thank you, sir.
Thank you so much, sir.